cantonfair.org.cn 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

Last updated:  May 24th, 2018

China Foreign Trade Centre and China Foreign Trade Centre (Group) (hereinafter refereed to as “CFTC” or us) respect your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains who we are, how we collect, share and use personal information about you, and how you can exercise your privacy rights. 

This Privacy Policy applies to personal information that we collect through our websites at [www.cftc.org.cn](http://www.cftc.org.cn/), [www.cantonfair.org.cn ](http://www.cantonfair.org.cn/)(“Websites”), as well as personal information that we collect when you use our services ("including but not limited to our websites, APP, official accounts"), such as applying for services at China Import and Export Fair (shortly known as Canton Fair).

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

 **What does CFTC do?**

CFTC is directly affiliated to China’s Ministry of Commerce; it is mainly responsible for organizing China Import and Export Fair (also known as the Canton Fair). At the meantime, CFTC owns and operates the modern Canton Fair Complex in Pazhou Island of Haizhu District and National Exhibition and Convention Center (Shanghai) in western central business district of Hongqiao, Shanghai. Moreover CFTC plays a dominant role in China’s exhibition industry for its professional exhibition experience and service as well as outstanding performance for over 60 years.

China Foreign Trade Centre (Group), a business entity affiliated to China Foreign Trade Centre, mainly organizes large and specialized exhibitions, and operates the Canton Fair Complex and National Convention and Exhibition Center (Shanghai). It also covers business such as e-commerce, advertising, import and export, tourism, hotel, restaurant, property etc. through its subsidiary, holding company, or joint-stock company.

For more information about CFTC, please refer to “Brief Introduction of CFTC” on [www.cftc.org.cn](http://www.cftc.org.cn/).

 **What personal information does CFTC collect and why?**

The personal information that we may collect about you broadly falls into the following categories:

 **Information that you provide voluntarily**

In order to use our services, we may ask you to provide personal information voluntarily such as

-Contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, fax number, gender and

-Pictures of your ID for business use and your pictures and

-Information that may help us provide and improve our services, such as your company name, company type, company size, your position, sourcing demands and

-Personal information that we collect through questionnaires, surveys or other marketing activities and

-Personal information that we provide to customer service agents to investigate or solve a problem and

-Passport number, nationality, country of residence.

We use this personal information to facilitate your attending the Canton Fair, provide you with other information and service of other events hosted by CFTC, and to provide you with information about us. The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

 **Information that we collect automatically**

When you visit our Websites, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. In some countries, including members of the European Union, this information may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.

Specifically, the information we collect automatically may include information like your IP address, device type, unique device identification numbers, browser-type, broad geographic location and other technical information. We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our Websites, including the pages accessed and links clicked. 

Collecting this information enables us to better understand the visitors who come to our Websites, where they come from, and what content on our Websites is of interest to them. We use this information for our internal analytics purposes and to improve our services.

Some of this information may be collected using cookies and similar tracking technology, as explained further under the heading “Cookies and similar tracking technology” mentioned in this Policy.

 **Information that we obtain from third party sources**

From time to time, we may receive personal information about you from third party sources, but only where we have checked that these third parties either have your consent or are otherwise legally permitted or required to disclose your personal information to us. 

The types of information we collect from third parties include information provided by professional exhibition organizations and other event assistance parties. We use the information we receive from these third parties to provide services to you, and maintain the accuracy of the records we hold about you.

In general, we will use the personal information we collect from you only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or for purposes that we explain to you at the time we collect your personal information. However, we may also use your personal information for other purposes that are incompatible with the purposes we have disclosed to you (such as purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes, or statistical purposes) if and where this is permitted by applicable data protection laws.

 **Who does CFTC share my personal information with?**

We may disclose your personal information to the following categories of recipients:

CFTC, third party service providers and partners who provide data processing services to us (for example, professional agencies that provides technical support for the services on our Websites), or who otherwise process personal information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Policy or notified to you when we collect your personal information;

We consider the disclosure of your personal information is necessary under the following circumstances:

   as a matter of applicable law or regulation:

to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights,

to protect your vital interests or those of any other person, we may disclose the information to any competent law enforcement body, regulatory agency, government agency, court or other third party.

to any other person with your consent to the disclosure.

 **Legal basis for processing personal information (EU visitors and customers only)**

If you are a visitor or customer from the European Union, our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. 

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only 

(i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you;

(ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights; 

(iii) where we have your consent to do so. 

In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). 

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will normally be to operate our events and communicating with you as necessary to provide our services to you and for our legitimate commercial interest, for instance, when responding to your queries, improving our services, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities. We may have other legitimate interests and if appropriate we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on how we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading.

Cookies and similar tracking technology 

We use cookies and similar tracking technology (collectively, “Cookies”) to collect and use personal information about you, including to serve interest-based advertising. For further information about the types of Cookies we use, why, and how you can control Cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.

 **How does CFTC keep my personal information secure?**

We use appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect the personal information that we collect and process about you. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information.

 **Data retention**

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal requirements). When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

 **Your data protection rights**

If you are a resident of the European Union, you have the following data protection rights:

If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading. 

In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading below.

You have the right to opt-out of exhibition information and service we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the e-mails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, then please contact us using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading below.

Similarly, if we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

 **Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you. We will obtain your consent to any material Privacy Policy changes if and where this is required by applicable data protection laws. You can see when this Privacy Policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us:

Domestic: 4000-888-999 

International: 86-20-888-999

Email: [info@cantonfair.org.cn](mailto://info@cantonfair.org.cn)

The data controller of your personal information is China Foreign Trade Centre (Group).
